[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "1 + 1?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "2",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "2 + 2?",
    "variants": ["3", "2", "5", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "4",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "3 + 3?",
    "variants": ["6", "2", "3", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "6",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "4 + 4?",
    "variants": ["8", "2", "3", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "8",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "5 + 5?",
    "variants": ["1", "10", "3", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "10",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "6 + 6?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "12", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "12",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "7 + 7?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "3", "14"],
    "trueAnswer": "14",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "8 + 8?",
    "variants": ["16", "2", "3", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "16",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "9 + 9?",
    "variants": ["1", "18", "3", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "18",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "10 + 10?",
    "variants": ["1", "20", "3", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "20",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "question": "11 + 11?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "22", "4"],
    "trueAnswer": "22",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "question": "12 + 12?",
    "variants": ["1", "2", "3", "24"],
    "trueAnswer": "24",
    "numberOfAnswers": 2
  }
]
